In the red
corner, we had
the young and
unchunnaged.
So, Mick, you're
going down in
the fourth.
Is that clear?
Just make sure
he doesn't kill
me. What a
fucking force.
So, give it
up for the
bone crunching.
One punch machine
gun.
And Mick!
Oh, no!
And then the
other corner...
Now, now he
looks like a
fanfucker.
Well, he's a
fanfucker, but he's
dirty and he's
dangerous.
Come on! Don't
not bend!
All right, it
is.
I'm trying to
look at the
fan.
Ritz!
I get ready!
To roll!
Oh, run, now!
Ritz!
Do you realize
I've just done
fucking 40 grand,
damn you?
What's the fucking
correct?
I'll make it
up to you.
All right, fuck
you, let me
break top.
I'll make it
up to you.
I promise, stay
in on me.
Oh, fucking pipe
is putty in
it.
Well, thanks for
the tip, break
top.
You're so new,
fucking fringe.
If I throw
a dog a
bone, I don't
want to know.
It tastes good
or not.
You stop me
again whilst I'm
walking and I'll
catch you.
Fucking jagas all.